老鼠从洞里出来了
Our rat's just come out of his den.
"基地"组织
Al-Qaeda?
爱尔兰共和军最近也不太安分
The IRA have been getting restless again,
-他们可能蠢蠢欲动  -对了
- maybe they're going to make an appearance... - Yes, yes, yes, yes!
我真是个白痴  蠢透了
I've been an idiot, a blind idiot!
-怎么了  -太好了  棒极了
- What? - Oh, that's good. That could be brilliant!
你想到什么了
What are you on about?
麦考夫的情报一点也不模糊
Mycroft's intelligence is not nebulous at all,
是非常详细  很具体
it's specific, incredibly specific.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
不是地下网络
It's not an underground network,
约翰  是地铁网络
John, it's an Underground network!
懂了
Right.
-什么  -有时候当一个大胆得离谱时
- What? - Sometimes a deception is so audacious,
反而不会被发现
so outrageous that you can't see it
威斯敏斯特/2号站台
哪怕事实就在眼前
even when it's staring you in the face. Look,
威斯敏斯特/2号站台
七节车厢驶离威斯敏斯特
seven carriages leave Westminster.